Hojjat Mehri-Tekmeh

Isfahan, IR

(+98)9134052885

www.HojjatMehri.com

HojjatMehri@gmail.com

stackoverflow.com/hojjat-mehri

github.com/hojjat-mehri

linkedin.com/hojjat-mehri

A professional with 17 years industrial experience with proven ability to manage the responsibilities of a development team. Enjoying being part of a successful and productive team acting as senior/lead developer by working closely with product owners and providing creative solutions to problems effectively.

Developing Experience

[DES 2016 - APR2022]

Manager of Development Department / Vista Team Co, Iran

Leading a technical team with 10 members, working closely with product owners in the agile company, developing and maintaining Phone Applications Connected to Web Site. Manager of the Development Department – Android and IOS developer – Project analyzer

[APR 2014 - DES 2016]

Freelancer Developer / Iran

Analyzing and developing most of projects in several Languages such as ASP.net, Windows and Android as freelancer.

[OCT 2013 - APR 2014]

Android Developer / EMA Co, Iran

Key member of development team, one of the roles were to plan and prioritize tasks at hand, coordinated all actions within the group.

[SEP 2006 – OCT 2013]

Freelancer Developer / Iran

Developing Windows applications by C# as freelancer

Skills

- Flutter Dart programming
- Android Programming with Java in Android Studio
- IOS Programming with Swift in XCode

- Kotlin, JAVA, Swift, Dart, Flutter, Python
- C++, C#, VB, SQL Server, SQLite
- SOLID, DRY, MVC, MVVM
- HTML, CSS, ASP.Net, JavaScript
- PHP, WordPress, Joomla
- Git, CI/CD, DevOps,
- Retrieval information, Data mining, Data privacy, Natural Language Processing

Education

[OCT 2017 - PRESENT]

PHD Student of Computer Software / Azad Najaf Abad University,

Iran

Right now, I'm student in PHD level in Computer Software Engineering. Dedicated on Big data, Text mining, Privacy in data mining, Information retrieval,

[SEP 2017]

MSc Information Computer Software / Azad Najaf Abad

University, Iran

Dedicated on Software engineering, Data Structure and Algorithm, AI, Distributed operating system, Distributed data, Data mining, Privacy in data mining. Title of these: "Improve the Speed of Plagiarism Detection in Persian Texts by Using BLAST".

[SEP 2013]

BSc Computer Software/ Aghigh, Iran

Studied Data Structure and Algorithm, AI, Software engineering, Operating system, C++ Programming language, OOP programming language, Web programming, Relational Database.

Educational Research Interests

- Data mining
- Privacy in data mining
- Text mining
- Plagiarism detection

- Big data
- Privacy preserving data mining
- 10
- Retrieval information

Publications

[SEP 2017]

Master's thesis

Title of these: "Improve the Speed of Plagiarism Detection in Persian Texts by Using BLAST".

[SEP 2016]

I had published a survey paper in Persian conference titled: "A review of content-based plagiarism detection methods" https://www.civilica.com/Paper-ITCC03_180.html

Teaching Experience

[SEP 2006 - PRESENT]

Teacher / Iran

I teach Android programming, C# programming, C++ Programming and.... in some institute and universities. I like to share my knowledge with others.

I love teaching and I teach about 12 years. I was a teacher in many institutes. It is obvious I teach computer science. different courses from ICDL (12 years ago) to professional Windows and Android programming. since 2014 I am a teacher at university. I taught in different universities with different courses like C++, C#, ASP.Net, Java, Android, SQL Server, Data Base Structure, OOP, Software Engineering and so on. I love teaching because "One child, one teacher, one book, one pen can change the world."

[SEP 2015 - MAY 2016]

Mohajer Technical University

Advanced programming, Web programming, Software Engineering

[JAN 2015 – MAY 2016]

Soroush Technical University

Advanced programming, Software Engineering

[SEP 2014 - MAY 2015]

Khaarazmi Technical University

Advanced programming, Web programming, Software Engineering, C# Programming, Graphic

[JUN 2016 - PRESENT]

Sobhan Institute

Android programming, C# Programming